<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>life on </title>
    <link>https://iulises32.github.io/blog/tags/life/</link>
    <description>Recent content in life on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 May 2021 18:08:02 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://iulises32.github.io/blog/tags/life/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>My Self</title>
      <link>https://iulises32.github.io/blog/post/my-self/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 May 2021 18:08:02 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iulises32.github.io/blog/post/my-self/</guid>
      <description>Who am I? I am Ulises Israel Zárate López, a 20 year old boy who lives in Mexico. I am currently studying Physics in the local university of my state, in 4th semester to be precise, almost finishing it. I have two older brothers, a sister and a brother, with whom I live together with my mother. My dad passed away when a I was 6.  What I like I love all the sciences but more physics and mathematics, the feeling of solving a problem after multiple hours of trying solving it makes me feel really good, and even more when everything fits and makes sense; that feeling when you finally understand what is going on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pets</title>
      <link>https://iulises32.github.io/blog/post/pets/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 May 2021 18:07:27 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iulises32.github.io/blog/post/pets/</guid>
      <description>My furry friend Something that equates with my love for physics are cats, I really love them, they are cute, funny, playful, curious, etc. Since I was a kid I&amp;rsquo;ve loved cats, they are fluffy and adorable, although sometimes are little demons that love the chaos, but who can blame them? For their cuteness everything is forgiven.
I&amp;rsquo;ve had other pets, actually a lot: birds, fishes, turtles, hamsters (a lot), rabbits, dogs, and chickens, but no one is compared with cats.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
